Hey wassup guys! My name is The Cherno. Welcome back to my C++
series. Today we gonna take what we learn our
classes so far and haven't gone actually writing a class from scratch.
Am not gonna take it too far today, we're not gonna write some
massive complicated class. We're just gonna write a basic log class
that should demonstrate some of the basic phases we have learnt so far.
Over the next few episodes we're going to keep working on this class and so introduce new concepts  so you get to see the process
and the difference from a basic version of class
to a more advanced version that does the same thing but  could be considered as a
better card.But first this video
Alright, so let's talk about this Log class that we're about to write
What is Log class? So this Log class is going to be a way
for us to manage a log messages . So another way it's
messages or information that we want our program
to print to the console.
This is usually used for debugging purposes and really helps us out
in out game or application, if we wanna kinda see what's going on
and just print the status of things into our console
because the console in our application is really like an information dump
which we can use to just print out what's going on
in our game or something that might be a little
different and it might not work all the time
because if there is something wrong with our graphics rendering system or something like that
we might not get those messages printing properly, however,
a console? is something that basically is built into the operating system
so we can pretty much guarantee that will always work
I also really like the idea of using a log class
as an example because a logging system can be
as simple or as complicated as you wanted to be
it's amazing how complicated some log
systems are like. I am talking 1000 of lines
of code just to print out to the console and
it's so so important for debugging and for development
that it is definitely worth spending time on that.